joblistghana.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy - Joblistghana.com - Jobs in Ghana

**Updated 26th September 2012  **

******WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS:**

**Joblist Ghana** **  takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using our contact form above.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our strong commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy only applies to any data gathered on the JoblistGhana.com web site (the “Site”), and does not apply to any other information or web site you may be visiting. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This Privacy Policy is effective as of 26th September 2012. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. You agree that by using the website you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails or job alerts if subscribed to.

At JoblistGhana.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by joblistghana.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Joblistghana.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable, in other words we know that a user visited but we don’t know who they are

We do not sell our users’ personal information to anyone for any reason what so ever, When posting jobs and resumes, our users are directed to the 3rd party (Employers website) where they decide for themselves how much contact information they wish to display.

**Google and DoubleClick Dart Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on joblistghana.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to joblistghana.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on joblistghana.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see in order to serve you better.

JoblistGhana.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by Google or any 3rd third-party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Some Important Tips To Use When Dealing With Prospective Employers**

  *        Never provide bank numbers or monetary transaction of any sort to any prospective employer
  *        Be cautious when dealing with contacts you are not comfortable with.
  *        Do not provide any non-work related personal information over the phone or online.  
****

**Email and Online Fraud**

Unfortunately, email and online fraud are continuing concerns for virtually all businesses and organizations that operate on the Internet. Please be aware that, Joblist Ghana can never request for your personal information either online or offline. If you receive an email or pop-up window requesting that you sign in to JoblistGhana.com and provide your bank or credit card information, do not respond. If you suspect any fraud, send us an email through [jobs@joblistghana.com](mailto:admin@joblistnigeria.com) and we will take appropriate actions.

**Joblist Ghana**

UK Contact Details:

Surflinks Limited  
14A Pitmedden Terrace  
Aberdeen  
AB10 7HR

Tel: +44(0)1224 901129

or    +44(0)77 35509992
